Finding Aid of the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1923-2015, UWM Manuscript Collection 139; 257.9 cubic ft. (741 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives
  - 7. Audio-Visual Materials, 1937-2015
    - 7B. Audio Cassettes and Digital Audio Files, 1983-2015
      - Annual Meetings
        - 1983, 48 audio cassettes (Box 391)
        - 1984, 49 audio cassettes (Box 391)
        - 1986, 118 audio cassettes (Box 392)
        - 1987, 84 audio cassettes (Box 393)
        - 1988, 70 audio cassettes (Box 400)
        - 1989, 7 audio cassettes (Box 530)
        - 1989, 120 audio cassettes (Box 394)
        - 1990, 144 audio cassettes (Box 395-396)
        - 1991, 108 audio cassettes (Box 396)
        - 1991, 36 audio cassettes (Box 400)
        - 1992, 12 audio cassettes (Box 529)
        - 1992, 132 audio cassettes (Box 397)
        - 1993, 120 audio cassettes (Box 497)
        - 1995, 144 audio cassettes (Box 398)
        - 1995, 8 beta tapes (Box 740)
        - 1996, 144 audio cassettes (Box 529)
        - 1996, 10 beta tapes (Box 740)
        - 1997, 78 audio cassettes (Box 728)
        - 1997, 1 beta tape (Box 741)
        - 1998, 160 audio cassettes (Box 528)
        - 1999, 176 audio cassettes (Box 530)
        - 2000, 32 audio cassettes (Box 528)
        - 2001, 192 audio cassettes (Box 523)
        - 2001, 55 audio cassettes (Box 730)
        - 2001, 218 audio cassettes (Box 731-733)
        - 2002, 187 audio cassettes (Box 690)
        - 2002, 24 audio cassettes (Box 729)
        - 2003, 208 audio cassettes (Box 691-692)
        - 2003-2007, 2015 (Electronic \Series 07\, Electronic Annual Meeting Recordings\)
        - 2004, 218 audio cassettes and 1 digital audio tape (Box 734-736)
        - 2005, 210 audio cassettes (Box 737-739)
        - 2007, 91 digital audio files (Electronic \Series 07\, Electronic Annual Meeting Recordings\, Electronic 2007\)
          Use CDs 23-46 access copies
        - 2009, 1 DVD-ROM; Missing (Box 741)
        - 2011, 1 DVD-ROM; Missing (Box 741)
      - Clinical Allergy Series
        - Part I: Immediate Hypersensitivity (IgE) Disorders, 1980, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part III: Bronchial Asthma, Section 2, 1980, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part VI: Uticaria, undated, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part VII: Adverse Reactions to Foods, undated, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part IX: Skin Testing, 1981, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part X: Atopic Dermatitis, 1982, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part XI: Allergic and Immunologic Diseases of the Eye, 1983, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part XII: Allergic Emergencies, 1983, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part XIII: Childhood Asthma, 1985, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part XIV: Nasal Cytology, undated, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
        - Part XV: The Differential Diagnosis, Evaluation and Treatment of Sinusitis, 1986, 1 audio cassette (Box 476)
      - Continuing Education
        - AAAAI/AAI/Clinical Immunology Society Joint Meeting, 1997, 160 audio cassettes (Box 399)
        - American Academy of Dermatology Dinner Workshop in NY, 1996, 2 audio cassettes (Box 739)
        - Adherence Planning Conference, 2005, 5 audio cassettes (Box 739)
        - AIDS/ARC: Update, 1986, 36 audio cassettes (Box 402)
        - Asthma 99: Theory and Treatment, 21 audio cassettes (Box 393)
        - Current Views in Allergy & Immunology, 1983, 8 audio cassettes (Box 403)
        - Current Views in Allergy & Immunology, 1986-1989, 12 audio cassettes (Box 531)
        - The First National Symposium on AIDS Prevention: Strategies for Curbing the Epidemic, 1987, 24 audio cassettes (Box 402)
        - Immunology Update, 1982, 6 audio cassettes (Box 403)
        - Intensive Review of Adult and Pediatric Allergy and Immunology, 1995, 32 audio cassettes (Box 692)
        - Interest Section Business Meeting, 1999, 6 audio cassettes (Box 542)
        - Lectures, undated, 10 audio cassettes (Box 403)
        - Presentations, 1988-1999, 7 audio cassettes (Box 542)
        - 2006 Pulmonary & Allergy Fellows Symposia, 1 DVD-ROM; Missing (Box 741)
        - 2007 Pulmonary & Allergy Fellows Symposia, 1 DVD-ROM; Missing (Box 741)
        - The XIII International Congress of Allergy & Clinical Immunology: Management of Allergy in the 1990s, 1988, 12 audio cassettes (Box 402)
    - 7C. Photographs, 1937-2013
      - American Board of Allergy and Immunology Exam Literature Review, 1991 (Box 430, Folder 63)
      - Arbesman, Carl, 1979, undated (Box 333, Folder 3)
      - Albert, Murray, undated (Box 430, Folder 1)
      - Alexander, Harry, undated (Box 333, Folder 1)
      - Allergy on NBC, Barbara Walters' "Not For Women Only," undated (Box 333, Folder 55)
      - Allergy Roundtable, 1954 (Box 332, Folder 3)
      - Amalgamation Committee, 1976 (Box 332, Folder 4)
      - American Academy of Allergy, Presidents Dinner, 1951 (Box 441)
      - American Association of Allergists, 1937 (Box 332, Folder 5)
      - Association for the Study of Allergy, 1930 (Box 441)
      - Association for the Study of Allergy, 8th Annual Meeting, 1930 (Oversize 1)
      - Anderson, John, 1980-1986, undated (Box 333, Folder 2)
      - Annual Meeting
        - 1950 (Box 441)
        - 1953-1974 (Binder 33)
        - 1975-1977 (Binder 34)
        - 1978 (Binder 1)
        - 1979 (Binder 2-5)
        - 1980 (Binder 6-11)
        - 1981-1982 (Binder 12)
        - 1983 (Binder 13)
        - 1984 (Binder 14-15)
        - 1985 (Binder 16-18)
        - 1986 (Binder 19-20)
        - 1987 (Binder 21-22)
        - 1988 (Binder 23)
        - 1989 (Binder 24)
        - 1990 (Binder 25)
        - 1991 (Binder 26)
        - 1992 (Binder 27)
        - 1993 (Binder 28)
        - 1994-1995 (Binder 29)
        - 1995, Slides (35 mm) (Box 334, Folder 9)
        - 1996 (Box 330-331)
        - 1997 (Binder 32)
        - 1998 (Binder 30)
        - 1998 (Box 722, Folder 1)
        - 1999 (Binder 31)
        - 1999-2013 (Electronic \Series 07\, Electronic Meeting Photos\)
        - 2000 (Binder 40)
        - 2000 (Box 722, Folder 2-10)
        - 2001 (Box 722, Folder 11)
        - 2005-2006 (Box 722, Folder 12-13)
        - Exhibit Halls, 1971-1976 (Box 332, Folder 1)
        - undated (Box 332, Folder 2)
        - Proof Sheets
          - 1976 (Box 333, Folder 56)
          - 1997 (Box 333, Folder 57)
          - 1998 (Box 333, Folder 58)
          - 1999 (Box 334, Folder 1)
          - 2000 (Binder 40)
      - Association for the Study of Allergy, 1930 (Box 441)
      - Association for the Study of Allergy, 1932 (Box 430, Folder 64)
      - Asthma '95, 1995 (Box 332, Folder 6)
      - Austen, K. Frank, 1967, undated (Box 333, Folder 4)
      - Award Recipients 1990-1995 (Box 332, Folder 7-13)
      - Baldwin, Horace, undated (Box 333, Folder 5)
      - Balyeat, Ray M., undated (Box 430, Folder 2)
      - Bernton, Harry S., undated (Box 430, Folder 3)
      - Biochemistry of Acute Allergic Reaction, Fifth International Symposium, 1988 (Box 332, Folder 14)
      - Black, J. Harvey, undated (Box 430, Folder 4)
      - Blumestein, George, 1979, undated (Box 333, Folder 6)
      - Board Members, 1980s-1990s (Box 722, Folder 14)
      - Board of Directors, Dinner, 1995 (Box 332, Folder 24)
      - Board of Directors, Meeting, undated (Box 334, Folder 2)
      - Bowlman, Katherine L, undated (Box 430, Folder 5)
      - Bronchoprovocation Workshop, 1978 (Box 332, Folder 15)
      - Brown, Aaron, undated (Box 430, Folder 6)
      - Buckley, Rebecca, undated (Box 333, Folder 7)
      - Buffum, William B., undated (Box 430, Folder 7)
      - Bullen, Stearns, undated (Box 333, Folder 8)
      - Burrage, Walter, undated (Box 333, Folder 9)
      - Busse, William, undated (Box 333, Folder 10)
      - Campbell, Dan, undated (Box 430, Folder 8)
      - Caulfield, Alfred H. W., undated (Box 430, Folder 9)
      - Chase, Merrill, undated (Box 430, Folder 10)
      - Chobot, Robert, undated (Box 333, Folder 11)
      - Clarke, J. Alexander, undated (Box 430, Folder 11)
      - Coca, Arthur F., undated (Box 430, Folder 12)
      - Cohen, Milton B., undated (Box 333, Folder 12)
      - Cohen, Sheldon, undated (Box 430, Folder 13)
      - Cole, Rufus, undated (Box 430, Folder 14)
      - Coleman, Monroe, undated (Box 430, Folder 15)
      - Cooke, Robert, undated (Box 333, Folder 13)
      - Criep, Leo H., undated (Box 333, Folder 14)
      - Dale, Sir Henry, undated (Box 430, Folder 16)
      - Dixon, Frank J., undated (Box 430, Folder 17)
      - Donnally, Harry H., undated (Box 430, Folder 18)
      - Duke, William, undated (Box 430, Folder 19)
      - Durham, Oren C., undated (Box 430, Folder 20)
      - Dworetzky, Murray, undated (Box 333, Folder 15)
      - Ellis, Elliot, 1987 (Box 333, Folder 16)
      - Executive Committee
        - Group Photograph, 1943-1991 (Box 332, Folder 25)
        - Meeting, 1972 (Box 430, Folder 62)
        - Meeting, 1979 (Box 332, Folder 26)
        - Meeting, 1981 (Box 332, Folder 27)
        - Meeting, 1988 (Box 332, Folder 28)
        - Meeting, 1992 (Box 332, Folder 29)
        - Meeting, undated (Box 332, Folder 30)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 332, Folder 31)
        - Retreat, 1992 (Box 332, Folder 32)
        - Retreat, 1994 (Box 332, Folder 33)
      - Eyerman, Charles H., undated (Box 430, Folder 21)
      - Farr, Richard, 1967? (Box 333, Folder 17)
      - Federal Drug Administration, Meeting, 1988 (Box 332, Folder 16)
      - Feinberg, Samuel, undated (Box 333, Folder 18)
      - 50th Anniversary Poster, 1992 (Box 441)
      - Figley, Karl, undated (Box 333, Folder 19)
      - Fink, Jordan, undated (Box 333, Folder 20)
      - Friedlander, Sidney, undated (Box 430, Folder 22)
      - Friedman, Harold, undated (Box 430, Folder 23)
      - Gay, Leslie, undated (Box 430, Folder 24)
      - Gilman, Alfred, undated (Box 430, Folder 25)
      - Glaser, Jerome, undated (Box 430, Folder 26)
      - Guy, Ruth A., undated (Box 430, Folder 27)
      - Hall, Harvey M., undated (Box 430, Folder 28)
      - Hampton, Stanley, undated (Box 333, Folder 21)
      - Hansel, French K., undated (Box 430, Folder 29)
      - Hill, Lewis Webb, undated (Box 430, Folder 30)
      - Hooker, Sanford, undated (Box 430, Folder 31)
      - Huber, Harry, undated (Box 430, Folder 32)
      - International Congress of Allergology and Clinical Immunology, 1985 (Box 722, Folder 15)
      - Ishizaka, Kimishage and Teruko, undated (Box 333, Folder 22)
      - Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, Editorial Board, 1992 (Box 332, Folder 17)
      - Kabat, Elvin, undated (Box 430, Folder 33)
      - Kailin, Eloise W., undated (Box 430, Folder 34)
      - Kaplan, Allen P., undated (Box 333, Folder 23)
      - Keeney, Edmund, undated (Box 333, Folder 24)
      - Kern, Richard A., undated (Box 430, Folder 35)
      - Kids Posters, 1996?, Slides (35 mm) (Box 722, Folder 16)
      - Koessler, Karl K., undated (Box 430, Folder 36)
      - Krause, Richard, undated (Box 333, Folder 25)
      - Layman, Barbara, 1983? (Box 333, Folder 26)
      - Lieberman, Phillip, undated (Box 333, Folder 27)
      - Lockey, Richard, 1980-1987 (Box 333, Folder 28)
      - Longcope, Warfield T., undated (Box 430, Folder 37)
      - Lowell, Francis, undated (Box 333, Folder 29)
      - Mackenzie, George M., undated (Box 430, Folder 38)
      - Malkiel, Saul, undated (Box 430, Folder 39)
      - Matthews, Kenneth, undated (Box 333, Folder 30)
      - Maynard, Edwin P., undated (Box 430, Folder 40)
      - Middleton, Elliot, Jr., undated (Box 333, Folder 31)
      - New York Allergy Society, Robert Cooke Dinner, 1958 (Box 441)
      - Noah, Joseph, undated (Box 333, Folder 32)
      - Norman, Philip S. (Box 430, Folder 41)
      - O'Keefe, Edward S., undated (Box 430, Folder 42)
      - Orange, Bob, 1967 (Box 333, Folder 4)
      - Osgood, Howard, undated (Box 430, Folder 43)
      - Paddock, Royce, undated (Box 430, Folder 44)
      - Patterson, Roy, 1979, undated (Box 333, Folder 33)
      - Peshkin, M. Murray, undated (Box 430, Folder 45)
      - Pierson, William, 1980-1981, 1985, undated (Box 333, Folder 34)
      - Piness, George, undated (Box 333, Folder 35)
      - President's Dinner, AAA, 1951 (Box 332, Folder 19)
      - Program Committee 1979-1981 (Box 332, Folder 20-22)
      - Rackerman, Francis M., undated (Box 430, Folder 46)
      - Rappaport, Ben, undated (Box 333, Folder 37)
      - Ratner, Bret, ca. 1955 (Box 333, Folder 36)
      - Reed, Charles, undated (Box 333, Folder 38)
      - Regional, State, and Local Allergy Societies, Board of Governors Retreat, 1992 (Box 334, Folder 3)
      - Regional, State, and Local Allergy Societies, Board of Governors, 1996, 1997 (Box 331, Folder 2)
      - Reisman, Robert, 1981? (Box 333, Folder 39)
      - Rose, Bram, 1979 (Box 333, Folder 40)
      - Rowe, Albert, undated (Box 430, Folder 47)
      - Salvaggio, John, undated (Box 333, Folder 41)
      - Sampler, Max, undated (Box 333, Folder 42)
      - Schloss, Oscar, undated (Box 430, Folder 48)
      - Seebohm, Paul, undated (Box 333, Folder 43)
      - Selfridge, Grant, undated (Box 430, Folder 49)
      - Sheffer, Albert, 1988?, undated (Box 333, Folder 44)
      - Sheldon, John M., undated (Box 430, Folder 50)
      - Sherman, William, undated (Box 333, Folder 45)
      - Siegel, Sheldon, undated (Box 430, Folder 51)
      - Sinusitis Symposium, 1992 (Box 332, Folder 23)
      - Slavin, Raymond, undated (Box 333, Folder 46)
      - Society for the Study of Allergy and Allied Conditions, 15th Annual Meeting, 1939 (Box 441)
      - Spain, William, undated (Box 333, Folder 47)
      - Squier, Theodore, undated (Box 333, Folder 48)
      - Staff, 1980s-1990s (Box 722, Folder 17)
      - Stein, David I. (Box 430, Folder 53)
      - Sulzberger, Marion, undated (Box 430, Folder 54)
      - Swineford, Oscar, undated (Box 333, Folder 49)
      - Talmage, David W., undated (Box 430, Folder 55)
      - Tuft, Louis, undated (Box 430, Folder 56)
      - Unidentified Photographs, 1992-1995? undated (Box 334, Folder 4-8)
      - Vallery-Radot, Pasteur, undated (Box 333, Folder 50)
      - Van Ardsel, Paul, Jr., undated (Box 333, Folder 51)
      - Van Metre, Thomas E., undated (Box 430, Folder 57)
      - Vander Veer, Albert, undated (Box 430, Folder 58)
      - Vaugh, John, undated (Box 333, Folder 52)
      - Vaughan, Warren T., undated (Box 430, Folder 59)
      - Walzer, Eugene, undated (Box 430, Folder 60)
      - Walzer, Matthew, undated (Box 430, Folder 61)
      - Wasserman, Stephen, undated (Box 333, Folder 53)
      - Winkenwerder, W. L., undated (Box 333, Folder 54)
  - 8. Continuing Medical Education, 1979, 1981, 1985-2010
    This series contains information on programs and seminars for doctors, nurses, and the allied health field including Allied Health, the Distinguished Lecture Series, Dialogues in Allergy, and the Managed Care Focus Series.
    - AAAAI and American Academy of Dermatology Combined Meeting Program, 2003 (Box 490, Folder 14)
    - AAAAI/ACAAI Certification and Maintenance of Certification Board Review Course, 2008 (Electronic \Series 08\, Electronic AAAAI-ACAAI Certification and Maintenance of Certification Board Review 2008\)
      Use CD 51 access copy
    - ACAAI Exam Review, 2007 (Electronic \Series 08\, Electronic ACAAI Exam Review 2007\)
    - ACAAI Exam Review, 2008 (Electronic \Series 08\, Electronic ACAAI Exam Review 2008\)
    - Activities Calendar, 1986-1993 (Box 492, Folder 1)
    - Advances in Asthma and Allergy, 1994 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - Advances in Asthma Care, 1991-1993 (Box 455, Folder 34)
    - Advances in Pediatric Rhinitis and Sinusitis, 1998, undated (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - Aeroallergen Course Toward Certification, 1993 (Box 380, Folder 5)
    - Allergic Diseases State of the Art Simulcast, 1993 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - Allergies, circa 2010 (Electronic \Series 08\, Electronic Allergies\)
    - Allergy and Asthma Disease Management Center, 1997 (Box 671, Folder 1)
    - Allergy and Asthma Disease Management Center, Physician's Online, 1996-1998 (Box 671, Folder 2)
    - Allergy and Asthma: Update '99, 1999 (Box 537, Folder 92)
    - Allergy and Clinical Immunology, 1994 (Box 490, Folder 7)
    - Allergy and Clinical Immunology for the Health Care Professional, 1990 (Box 455, Folder 35)
    - Allergy and Immunology 2001, 2001, 6 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 532)
    - Allergy and Immunology and Clinical and Laboratory Immunology Training Program Directory
      - 1981 (Box 380, Folder 7)
      - 1993 (Box 380, Folder 9)
      - 1995, 1998/1999 (Box 380, Folder 10-11)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 491, Folder 5)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 540, Folder 59)
    - Allergy and Immunology for the Practicing Physician, 1986 (Box 380, Folder 8)
    - Allergy and Immunology GME Surveys, Center for Health Workforce Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 447, Folder 52)
    - Allergy and Immunology Review for Re-Certification
      - 2001 (Box 455, Folder 37)
      - 2005, 2007 (Box 540, Folder 46)
    - Allergy for the Clinician, Practical Solutions to Everyday Problems, 1991 (Box 455, Folder 36)
    - Allergy Outreach-A Continuing Medical Education Opportunity, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 447, Folder 1)
    - Allergy Practice Management Seminar, 1995 (Box 455, Folder 38)
    - Allergy Update, 1993, 1995 (Box 380, Folder 12)
    - Allergy Update, 1996 (Box 490, Folder 4)
    - Allied Health
      - Administration, 1993 (Box 317, Folder 1)
      - Clinical Issues, 1993 (Box 317, Folder 2)
      - Executive Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 317, Folder 3)
      - General, 1990-1994 (Box 317, Folder 4)
      - Meetings, 1993 (Box 317, Folder 5)
      - Membership
        - 1989-1990 (Box 317, Folder 6)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 317, Folder 7)
        - Forms and Certificates, undated (Box 317, Folder 8)
      - Reading Lists, 1994-2000 (Box 317, Folder 9)
      - Regional Courses
        - 1993-1994 (Box 447, Folder 3)
        - Audiocassette Tapes, 1991, 7 audio cassettes (Box 320)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 317, Folder 10)
        - Handouts, undated (Box 317, Folder 11-13)
        - Invitations, 1990-1998 (Box 318, Folder 1)
        - Participants' Packets, 1990 (Box 318, Folder 2)
        - Syllabi
          - 1987-1990 (Box 318, Folder 3)
          - 1991-1993 (Box 318, Folder 4-6)
          - 1994-1995 (Box 319, Folder 1-5)
          - 1996-1997 (Box 320, Folder 1-3)
          - 1998 (Box 671, Folder 3)
      - Research, 1993 (Box 320, Folder 4)
      - Seminars, 1987-1989 (Box 320, Folder 5-7)
      - Southwestern Allergy Forum Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Annual Allergy Update, 1992 (Box 455, Folder 39)
    - Aspiration of Foreign Bodies in Children, 1979, Accompanying audio cassette in box 476 (Box 475, Folder 2)
    - Asthma, circa 2010 (Electronic \Series 08\, Electronic Asthma\)
    - Asthma ’95, 1995 (Box 380, Folder 13)
    - Asthma and Airway Allergies: Mechanisms and Management, 1992 (Box 455, Folder 40)
    - Asthma and Allergy in the Next Millennium, 1997 (Box 380, Folder 14)
    - Asthma Care and Patient Education: The Nurse's Role, 1990 (Box 368, Folder 14)
    - Asthma Consultants Postgraduate Course, 1993 (Box 455, Folder 41)
    - Asthma '99: Theory to Treatment, 1999 (Box 540, Folder 53)
    - Asthma: Pathogenesis and Physiologic Consequences, 1979 (Box 472, Folder 6)
    - Asthma: Principles of Asthma Treatment, 1979 (Box 472, Folder 7)
    - Asthma: Theory to Treatment, 1995 (Box 455, Folder 42)
    - Asthma Therapy: What you Need to Know to be an Expert Sub-Specialist, 2002 (Box 472, Folder 8)
    - Asthma Update: The Managed Care Perspective, 1992-1993 (Box 520, Folder 4)
    - Autumn Allergy Update, 1992 (Box 524, Folder 8)
    - Autumn Allergy Update, 1993-1995 (Box 381, Folder 1-3)
    - Basic Immunology for Clinicians Update, 2005 (Box 534, Folder 6)
    - Bronchiolitis, 1981 (Box 472, Folder 9)
    - Cancer Immunology, 1979, Accompanying audio cassette in box 476 (Box 475, Folder 3)
    - Capitalizing on Capitation: the Allergist and Managed Care, 1995-1996 (Box 520, Folder 13)
    - Chief Residents' Program
      - 1997, 1999 (Box 381, Folder 4-6)
      - 1998 (Box 520, Folder 6)
      - 2000 (Box 503, Folder 6)
    - Chrysalis Project
      - Annual Meeting
        - 2004 (Box 526, Folder 10)
        - 2005 (Box 540, Folder 37)
        - 2006 (Box 671, Folder 4)
      - Brochure, undated (Box 447, Folder 4)
    - Clinical Allergy and Immunology for the Practicing Physician, 1985-1987, 1990-1991, 1995 (Box 381, Folder 7)
    - Clinical Allergy for the Practicing Physician, 1986 (Box 540, Folder 5)
    - Clinical Allergy Series, Accompanying audio cassettes in box 476
      - Part I: Immediate Hypersensitivity (IgE) Disorders, 1980 (Box 472, Folder 10)
      - Part III: Bronchial Asthma, Section 2, 1980 (Box 472, Folder 11)
      - Part VI: Uticaria, undated (Box 475, Folder 4)
      - Part VII: Adverse Reactions to Foods, undated (Box 475, Folder 5)
      - Part IX: Skin Testing, 1981 (Box 472, Folder 12)
      - Part X: Atopic Dermatitis, 1982 (Box 472, Folder 13)
      - Part XI: Allergic and Immunologic Diseases of the Eye, 1983 (Box 472, Folder 14)
      - Part XII: Allergic Emergencies, 1983 (Box 473, Folder 1)
      - Part XIII: Childhood Asthma, 1985 (Box 473, Folder 2)
      - Part XIV: Nasal Cytology, undated (Box 473, Folder 3)
      - Part XV: The Differential Diagnosis, Evaluation and Treatment of Sinusitis, 1986 (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - Clinical Cutaneous Allergy and Immunology, 1996, 1999 (Box 381, Folder 8)
    - Clinical Immunology
      - Part I: Basic Immunology-B-Call Immunity, undated, Accompanying audio cassette in box 476 (Box 473, Folder 5)
      - Part II: Basic Immunology: T-Cell Immunity Phagocytosis and Complement, undated, Accompanying audio cassette in box 476 (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - Clinical Immunology Update, undated, Accompanying audio cassette in box 476 (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - Compass: New Directions in the Treatment of Allergic Conjunctivitis and Related Disorders, 2002 (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - Comprehensive Review in Adult and Pediatric Allergy/Immunology
      - 1991, 1995 (Box 455, Folder 43-44)
      - 1993, 1997 (Box 381, Folder 9)
    - Continuing Education Information, 1941, undated (Box 447, Folder 5)
    - Controversies in the Treatment of Rhino-Sinusitis, 1994 (Box 381, Folder 10)
    - Current Issues and Emerging Controversies in Allergy and Immunology, 1998 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Current Trends in the Management and Treatment of Rhino-Sinusitis, 1994-1996 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - Current Views
      - Allergen Immunotherapy, 2002 (Box 686, Folder 1)
      - Allergic Skin Disease, 2002, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 2)
      - Chronic Hyperplastic Eosinophilic Sinusitis, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 3)
      - Factitious Allergic Disease, 2002, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 4)
      - Hidden Food Allergies, 2001, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 5)
      - Hygiene, Allergy and Asthma, 2002, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 6)
      - Occupational Asthma, 2002, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 7)
      - Practice Parameters for Allergic Rhinitis, 2001, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 8)
      - Update on Immunizations, 2000, 2002, Includes audio cassette (Box 686, Folder 9)
    - Current Views in Allergy and Immunology
      - 1981-1982, Includes slides and audio cassettes (Box 533, Binder 7-9)
      - 1983-1984, Includes slides and audio cassettes (Box 403, Binder 10-11)
      - 1986-1990, Includes slides and audio cassettes (Box 531, Binder 15-18)
      - 1990-1991, Includes slides and audio cassettes (Box 532, Binder 19)